Love Continues
Red Nose Day Actually is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Richard Curtis.
Fourteen years after the events of the first film, a series of encounters between people
in Britain reminds us that in these different times Love, actually exists.
The Prime Minister, played by Hugh Grant.
Daniel, played by Liam Neeson.
Jamie, played by Colin Firth.
Sarah (US version), played by Laura Linney.
Mark, played by Andrew Lincoln.
Peter, played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
Red Nose Day Actually is a 2017 British romantic comedy television short promotional film, following a dozen of the
characters from Richard Curtis' Christmas film Love Actually, as part of the fundraising event Red Nose Day 2017.
Curtis returns with many of the cast members from the original film including Hugh Grant, Liam Neeson, Colin Firth, Andrew Lincoln, Chiwetel Ejiofor,
Keira Knightley, Martine McCutcheon, Bill Nighy, Thomas Sangster, Lúcia Moniz, Olivia Olson, Marcus Brigstocke, and Rowan Atkinson.
The short film was first broadcast on BBC One on 24
March 2017, as a part of Red Nose Day.
A slightly different version of the film, featuring Laura Linney reprising her
role and Patrick Dempsey, was broadcast in the US on 25 May 2017.
The film explores themes of romcom, time, sequel, love, short film.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.